Australia
Marist College
Australia
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.1.5
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass Plate Negatives; Australia
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Indexed Photographs, 2.1.1.2.1
            - Australia, 2.1.1.2.5
                - Statue of Queen Victoria in Melbourne Botanical Garden, 1921; 61 (Box 1271)
                5x7
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, city in distance, 1921; 62
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, close-up of flower bush, 1921; 63
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, close-up of flower bush, 1921; 64
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, lily pond, city in distance, 1921; 65
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, near view, 1921; 66
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, close-up of lilies in pond, 1921; 67
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, lily pond and children on right, 1921; 1 (Box 1272)
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, lawn and big palms, rubber hose running across grass, 1921; 2
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, long row of flower bushes, 1921; 3
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, bushes covered with big clusters of flowers, 1921; 4
                - Melbourne Botanical Garden, flower bushes with one palm in back of them, statue of King Edward, 1921; 5
                - Perth, harbor and peninsula, 1921; 6
                - Perth, arm of bay, town in distance, 1921; 7
                - Perth, harbor, big tree in foreground, 1921; 8
                - Perth, harbor, shadow of tree on right, 1921; 9